export const QuizData = [
    {
        key:1,
        question: "When did French Revolution took place?",
        options:[ "1788", "1776", "1789", "1786"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        key:2,
        question: "When did Bhagat Singh hanged to death?",
        options:["31 May , 1931", "4 July , 1923", "23 March , 1931", "31 January , 1930"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        key:3,
        question: "Where was Subash Chandra Bose born?",
        options: ["Cuttak", "Kolkata", "Merrut" , "Varanasi"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        key:4,
        question: "Who were not the founding mmebers of HSRA?",
        options: ["Chandra Shekhar Azad", "Sukhdev", "Bhagat Singh", "Yashpal"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        key:5,
        question: "When did Soviet Union disintegrated",
        options: ["1999", "1998", "1997", "1990"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        key:6,
        question: "Who was the first president of Sovuet Union?",
        options: ["Vladimir Lenin", "Joseph Stalin", "Mao Zedong", "Gobaerchev"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        key:7,
        question: "In which country there was no regime chnge during Arab Spring?",
        options: ["Tunisia", "Morocco", "Egypt", "Saudai Arabia"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        key:8,
        question: "Who was the president of Libya during Arab Spring?",
        options: ["Muammar Gaddafi", "Saddam Hussain", "Kassim Sulemni", "Ben Ali"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        key:9,
        question: "Which is the only city located in two continents?",
        options: ["Mexico City", "St. Petersburg", "Istanbul", "Riyadh"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        key:10,
        question: "Which is the easternmost state of India?",
        options: ["Assam", "Mizoram", "Manipur", "Arunanchal Pradesh"],
        answer:4
    },
];